ANDRII ROI

Full Stack Software Engineer | Security Engineer



in LinkedIn Profile | м andriyroy3@gmail.com | 🖗 GitHub Profile



PROFILE

I am an experienced Software and Security Engineer with a passion for helping clients find solutions to their problems. I have extensive experience in the industry, including more than 3 years working as an information technology professional. I am highly organized, detail-oriented, and have strong communication skills.

EDUCATION

State university of **Telecommunications**

2015 - 2017

Masters degree in cybersecurity

CERTIFICATIONS | COURSES

- TryHackMe: Junior Penetration Tester path
- SANS: SEC542 Web Application Penetration Testing and Ethical Hacking
- APIUniversity: OWASP API Security Top 10
- LinkedIn: Advanced Web **Application Penetration Testing**

SKILLS

- Java 11+
- Maven
- Spring (Core, Boot, Security, Data)
- Hibernate
- ES(Javascript, Typescript)
- Angular, React
- Bootstrap, JQuery, Tailwind
- MySQL, PostgreSQL, h2, SQLite
- Python, Bash, Go (Non-main technologies)
- Web application security
- Security coding best practices
- Vulnerabilities assessment
- Web applications penetration testing
- Securing CI/CD

WORK EXPERIENCE

DEVSECOPS ENGINNER

October 2024 - present

First Ukrainian International Bank

- Securing development lifecycle
- Software development (automation, tools)
- Gig contract cooperation format
- Key technologies: OWASP, vulnerabilities scanners, fuzzers, red/blue team frameworks

JAVA FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SmartFoxPro Itd

July 2024 - August 2024

- Development frontend and backend part of features
- Bugfix
- Outstaff cooperation format
- Key technologies: Java 21, Angular 17, Typescript, Spring Boot, Spring Security, MySQL

SECURITY SOFTWARE ENGINEER | PENETRATION TESTER

NDA

March 2022 - Present

- Securing project lifecycle development
- Performing web application and network penetration tests
- Writing software for red team purposes
- Researching and implementation CVE's from Proof of Concept to Proof of Work
- Key technologies: Java 17, React, Python, C++, Javascript, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Docker
- Leading group of 5 engineers to accomplish cumstomers purposes

JAVA MENTOR

GoIT

November 2021 - September 2023

- Running Java Marathons
- Students technical support
- · Homework assessment and technical feedback
- New graduate project development

FULL STACK JAVA SOFTWARE ENGINEER | CYBERSECURITY ENGINEER

SmartFoxPro ltd.

April 2021 - March 2022

- As Software Engineer:
- Developing backend server logic for studying freelance platform
- Bug fixing
- New backed and frontend feature implementation.
- Key technologies: Java 8, Spring Boot, Spring Data, Javascript, AngularJS, Vaadin, MySQL, JQuery
- As Cyber Security Engineer:
- Implementation of government and international standarts in information security
- Analyzing networks and threats
- Vulnerabilities assesstment.